(Watch on www.kisskh.llc)
You feel so good.
Shit.
Yes, please.
Ah, shit.
Faster.
Yes.
You feel so good, Jeric!
You jerks!
Baby, I thought you were working overtime?
Is that so?
Huh?
And you, you're such a slut!
- Baby... That's enough, baby. - Was it good?
- Was it good in my bed? - That's enough.
- That's enough, baby! - Let go of me!
That's enough! That's enough, baby!
You slut!
That's enough!
- Let go of me, Jeric! - That's enough.
That's enough, baby.
Don't you dare call me baby!
So just because you knew
I was working overtime...
You brought a woman here in our bed!
- Huh? - Baby, I'm sorry.
Sorry?
- Sorry? - I'm sorry.
Screw your sorry!
You're only sorry...
because I caught you!
You're such a jerk, Jeric.
- Baby, I'm sorry. - I gave you everything...
And you still cheated on me.
Damn you!
I'm sorry.
Get out.
- I'm sorry, baby. - Get out!
- Baby, I'm sorry. - I don't need you here anymore.
Get out!
- I'm really sorry. - Leave now!
Karina, I'm really sorry.
I said leave!
Damn you!
Get out of here!
Yes, hello?
Girl, how are you?
What on earth happened to you?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Just recovering.
Oh dear.
Our boss is already looking for you.
You could lose your job, you know?
I know. I'm sorry about that.
You should know that I feel what you're feeling.
Fix yourself.
Look at yourself.
Maybe Jeric cheated on you--
Because he didn't find you attractive anymore.
Maybe you're right.
Thank you for the advice, Janna.
You know what, I'm recommending you to a hairdresser.
She has her own salon.
You should know that she's very good.
Go pay her a visit.
I'll send you the address.
Alright.
Good morning!
How may I help you?
Why? Is there a problem?
- Oh no, it's not that. - I'll be right back.
Are you...
Janna's hairdresser friend?
Yes, I am.
So you're the client she referred to me?
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry.
I didn't expect that you'd be a girl.
I'm just used to a gay person doing it.
Is that so?
Don't worry about it,
I was raised by a gay couple.
Come on, let's get you settled.
Okay.
You can put your bag over there.
Oh, thank you.
So, what kind of service do you want?
Uh...
Maybe, I'll leave that to you.
What you think will suit for someone...
who is brokenhearted.
Alright, leave it to me.
There you go. Look at your new hairstyle.
Do you like it?
Yes.
It's beautiful.
You know...
The hair really makes a difference for a woman.
A lot of women who are trying to move on
have their hair changed.
Maybe you're right.
If you need someone to talk to...
Just call me.
Thank you, Missy.
How are you?
I'm good. My new hairstyle helped.
Good to hear, I hope you feel better.
And then...
You're really spoiling me, huh?
Of course, it's you.
Come on. Then over here...
- There, see that? - Oh, what about there?
Yeah, let's check it out.
I think the food is better there.
Oh, absolutely.
The food is really great here in our place.
Okay.
- If you say so. - Of course.
Hello, Janna.
Can you be with me at my apartment tonight?
Oh no, I can't. I have a date tonight.
Why? What happened?
Oh, I see.
Oh, it's nothing.
Alright, sorry for disturbing.
Okay, if you say so.
I'm sorry too.
I'll just see you at work tomorrow.
Hello?
Hello, Missy?
So, what happened?
It's about my ex.
There he went.
I saw him with that girl again,
the one I caught him having sex with.
They're together.
The audacity.
I thought you're moving on already?
I know.
But why does it still hurt so much?
You know, I've been with that jerk for two years.
And he'll just throw it away with that slut?
You know what?
Let's drink to it.
Come on.
I'm sure you'll forget about it.
Thank you, Missy...
For coming to see me.
It's just that...
I feel like I'll lose it if I have no one to talk to.
Wow, this really warms you up, huh?
You know what?
You need to forget those worthless men.
If only it was that easy.
You shouldn't even be crying over him.
You're his loss.
Let me help you forget him.
Jeric...
I love you.
Does it really feel this sticky?
Oh yes.
This treatment can really feel sticky for your hair.
Just bear with me, okay?
You'll look great after.
The thing is...
This is actually my first time.
I haven't done this before but
it feels good.
That's why...
If you visit more often, your hair will turn out nice.
The hair is really a big deal for a woman's transformation.
Not only in the physical aspect...
But also for mental and emotional well-being.
And when you embrace that change...
You'll have a more positive outlook in life.
Missy?
About...
What happened between us last night.
What do you mean?
Please, Missy.
Stop hiding it already.
Something happened right?
I'm sorry about last night.
No.
Don't be sorry.
I didn't regret a single thing.
What about you?
You wanted it, right?
Oh my gosh, Karina. You're such a queen!
You're dating the hairdresser?
Yep, that's right.
You're driving me crazy, you're insane.
You're ridiculous.
Aren't you the one...
who should understand me the best for this?
Okay, fine, I get it.
But girl...
it's just surprising.
You fell in love with a lesbian?
Well...
Even me...
I never saw it coming.
But that's it.
It just happened.
You know what they say...
Love...
is love.
You never really know
when you fall for someone.
Who you fall for...
no matter the gender.
Well...
you have a point.
That reminds of a time when...
I realized that
I like men too.
I was so giddy!
Anyway...
Remember what I told you, okay?
Be happy.
Good luck with your relationship, okay?
Thank you, Janna.
Alright then.
I'll just see tomorrow at work, okay?
Okay, bye.
Why is this still here?
I'm so happy, Karina.
You're actually my first ever girlfriend.
Really, my love?
But did you always know you were into women?
Yeah.
I was already attracted to girls since I was young.
My adoptive gay mom already knew
the real me.
But she decided to
hide me so I won't get bullied
And so...
I ended up dating all kinds of men.
But...
It always failed.
Why?
Maybe because no matter what I do,
I know what I really want for myself.
That's okay, love.
Because I'm now here with you.
You don't need to be afraid anymore.
We don't need to be afraid anymore.
Right?
- Cheers! - Cheers!
This place seems nice.
Yeah.
Hi girls.
I see you love cocktail.
I guess...
You must love cock too.
Excuse me, sir...
We're not trying to be rude or anything,
but please...
Leave us alone, okay?
Relax.
Relax!
I just want to be friends.
Besides...
You're both girls.
What are you gonna do?
Scissor each other?
It's more fun with a guy around.
- Like me. - Disgusting.
What a creep.
Hey! Open up, bitch!
Oh, so you don't want to come out, huh?
Thank you for coming to see me, love.
Of course.
You're my girlfriend.
Wow, today was exhausting.
We had a lot of clients today.
But...
I'm glad you're here
because at least...
You make me feel easier.
You're so sweet.
I'm serious.
Here, take a bite.
Thank you.
That's so good.
- Where did you buy that? - Just somewhere around here.
To be fair, it's really good.
You want some fries?
The view here is so beautiful.
- Love? - Yes?
Do you think we'll last?
Hold on.
Why would you ask that?
No reason.
I just know how things are these days
that somehow...
relationships like these are already accepted.
But I don't know if...
we'll really last.
I guess...
yeah.
What matters is...
we love each other, right?
Do you think
you won't look for a man in your life anymore?
Oh my.
I'm gonna be late.
My break time is over.
I need to go back to the mall now, okay?
Okay love, take care okay?
You too, take care heading home.
I need to go.
I'll go ahead, okay?
- Bye, love. - Bye, love.
Jeric?
Karina.
I didn't know she was married to a soldier.
Then eventually...
we crossed paths.
I got beaten up when we were caught at his house.
You know what that's called?
Karma.
Serves you right.
Karina?
Can I stay over at your place for a while?
I've got nowhere else to go.
While I'm looking
for a place to stay.
I promise, once I can find a place...
I'll leave.
Karina...
I have a job now.
I'm now a taxi driver.
I got hired by an operator.
So by then
once I've saved enough...
I'll leave.
I think I know where this is going.
Karina, please.
Please.
Okay, fine, whatever.
You're so annoying.
Thank you so much...
Karina.
Karina?
What?
Do you have a boyfriend already?
No.
So...
Does this mean
we can start over again?
Gosh, you're impossible.
Come on, let's go home.
Jeric, what are you doing?
Can you not?
Don't just walk around here naked.
Look at you overreacting.
- As if this is your first time. - Can you stop?
We both know you already saw all of me.
Quit it!
Just so you know, we're not together anymore.
So stop, okay!
Oh please!
Don't you miss this?
Move out of the way.
What am I doing?
Get yourself together, Karina.
Love?
Are you okay?
Yes, why?
Nothing.
You seem to be bothered about something.
Ah...
You're just overthinking.
You're so sweet.
Oh, come on.
Why do that in public?
You're disgusting!
Your face and your attitude are disgusting!
You judge too much.
- Hey, that's enough. - Come on, son.
Just ignore her.
I could slap her just for saying those things.
Missy, enough.
Everyone's staring at us.
Wait a minute...
Why am I the one you are ashamed of?
Didn't you hear what she said?
I just don't want any trouble. Okay?
So please, just stop.
You don't need to freak out
every time something like this happens.
Because you already know, right?
Our relationship isn't normal for everyone.
So, what are we? Abnormal?
That's not what I meant.
Then what?
You know what, forget it.
Karina, what is it?
What do you mean "what is it"?
For such a small thing, you're gonna get mad?
My point is...
we don't need to react
to what people might say about us every time.
Fine. I'm sorry, okay?
I need to go back to work.
Let's just talk about this next time.
Jeric? What are you doing here?
Oh, nothing.
I just came to check on you.
You also forgot to lock the door.
Oh, right.
Uh...
I forgot you are back here again.
I'm already used to living alone.
You know...
Lotions feel better
when someone else is rubbing it on you.
Stop it, go on, get out of here.
- Wait, hold on. - Just leave.
Just hold on, Karina.
I know that...
I really messed up and hurt you.
But
I just want you to know that...
Karina...
I still love you.
If you hadn't made me leave back then...
You’re still the one I’d choose.
Karina...
I'm sorry, okay?
Let me show you
the things I've changed about myself.
So I hope...
you can forgive me.
You missed this, didn't you?
Right?
I know that you missed this, Karina.
Karina...
forgive me, okay?
Yes!
Let's eat, baby?
Okay.
Want me to feed you?
- Sure. - Here.
So sweet of you.
Is it good?
It's good.
Baby...
Did you miss me feeding you?
You're so naughty.
Oh, please.
What about last night?
- What? - You seemed so thirsty in bed.
Oh stop,
whatever.
I really missed you.
What?
- What is it? - I missed you so much.
You're so clingy.
Its like you didn't had enough of me last night.
Drink your coffee.
- Here. - It's a malunggay bread.
Have some more.
- Oh, that's salty. - Yeah.
Just a bit.
I really missed you.
I'll just drink this.
See.
- I told you it's hot. - You're right.
My God, Karina, are you serious?
Yeah.
I couldn't stop myself.
The truth is...
I really missed Jeric.
I thought
I already moved on but turns out...
I haven't.
What about Missy?
That's the problem
because...
I love them both.
Oh girl...
You can't love them both at once.
But that's what I feel.
The thing is...
They give different things in my life.
The feeling that...
I can't bear to lose them both.
But, girl...
You still need to choose sooner or later.
You can't love two people at the same time.
You're right.
But for now...
I'll just see how things will go.
Who really matters more to me between the two of them.
- Right? - Alright, if you say so.
That's all up to you.
I understand you, you know.
But until then
remember what I told you.
Take care.
Hi love.
You've been so distant lately.
Are you still mad at me?
Not really.
There's just a lot of...
customers these past few days.
Is that so?
But...
I really missed you.
Is that right?
You missed me?
Of course.
I missed you so much.
I'll prove it to you, Karina,
that this man is worthless.
No matter what you do,
he won't change.
Maybe I'll need you.
- Missy? - Yes.
You're even prettier in person than...
your pictures online.
So you're a charmer after all?
Nice to meet you.
So are we just gonna chat here?
Come on, get in.
So, where to?
Up to you.
No matter where you'll take me,
I'll just ride along.
Why did you stop here?
Missy, the thing is
I really can't afford a hotel room.
Oh, I see.
That's really not a problem.
We can do it anywhere.
Alright.
Wait.
Don't you worry.
You're gonna enjoy this.
What's taking her so long?
Love?
Where are you?
I'm at the salon, why?
I thought we're going to meet up?
You said you'd come and see me.
I'm sorry, I forgot.
I'm just swamped with work.
I'm really sorry.
It's just pretty busy at the salon right now.
I see.
Alright.
I understand.
I'll just call you again later, okay?
Okay.
Hi. Where are you?
Are you doing anything tonight?
Answer the phone, Jeric!
- Where have you been this time? - Huh?
Um... I was at work.
There were just a lot of passengers tonight.
I'd lose out on money if I went home right away.
Can't you even text me back or answer my calls?
Baby...
I was driving.
I could get into an accident, okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, okay?
Come on, let's sleep.
I know you're hiding something from me again, Jeric.
You're not going to hurt me the way you did before.
So as early as now...
I'll find out for myself.
Jeric: You're so good. Let's do it again soon!
Missy: Of course. As many as it takes, until you're tired.
Missy?
She is...
Jeric's other woman?
- Hey, love. - What took you so long?
I'm sorry, okay?
Well... The queue was so long.
I also had to fix some paperworks for my taxi.
Uh, ma'am, are you sure we're on the right place?
Yes, I'm sure.
Okay.
Sir, right here.
- Stop the car. - Hold on.
Wait a minute.
- Karina? - You assholes!
- What, Missy? What? - Hey!
- Are you gonna say something? - Wait!
- Stop! Stop it. - You stop!
This is between us, you asshole!
Have you been lying to me all this time?
What?
What? Are you going to say something to me?
Stop!
That's enough! Stop that!
That's enough!
Enough, both of you!
Damn you both!
How long have you been cheating on me?
Damn you.
You're a bitch, Missy!
You're worse!
Now you know how much it hurts!
Wait, hold on!
You guys know each other?
So she was the one you were seeing, Karina?
Yes.
You're a lesbian?
But when I found out you returned to Karina's life...
I got so mad.
That's why my plan was...
to make her realize that you're worthless.
What you should say is...
you enjoyed having sex with him, right?
That's why you continued,
and you became my boyfriend's...
other woman.
Stop pretending you have nothing to do with this,
you cheated first.
You're in a relationship, and you got back with your ex.
- You bitch. - Oh, is that so?
You're really shameless.
Damn you!
- Hey, stop it. - You're such a slut!
- That's enough! - Let go!
Let go of me!
Stop it, please.
We're here to sort this out.
Okay?
Also...
why can't the three of us just be together?
What?
It would be a win-win situation for the three of us, right?
You can share me both.
Then you can do whatever you want with your relationship.
And the best thing is...
We can have a threesome.
I won't share him with you.
Only one of us gets to have him.
No!
What are you doing?
- Stop it! - Missy, what are you doing?
Have you lost your mind?
You're mine, only mine.
Just stop, okay?
I want someone who will love me completely.
Even when I was still a child...
nobody ever wanted me.
Even my own family took me away.
And my mother, Rico...
she died and left me behind.
And Jeric?
I know that I am the one he wants,
and I know that he's ready to leave you for me.
That's enough, Missy.
Calm down.
Only one of us gets to live, Karina.
Jeric is mine.
Enough, okay?
Let's stop this, please.
I'm so sorry for everything I've done to you.
You should know that
you deserve to be loved.
It may not be me,
or Jeric...
I know there's someone who will love you completely
without anybody else.
So, that's enough, okay?
It's going to be okay.
Karina, I don't know what got into me last night.
Thank you that you still forgave me,
even if I almost ended up hurting you.
That's why, I have decided to stay away,
from you and Jeric.
I hope...
both of you will finally be happy together.
Are you really sure about your decision?
Yes, Jeric...
And I don't ever want to see you again.
I don't need you anymore.
Thank you...
Karina.